question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "category": "Vehicles",
     "question": "The Chevrolet Corvette has always been made exclusively with V8 engines only.",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it&#039;s entirety by Facebook for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "Linus Torvalds created Linux and Git.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The names of Tom Nook&#039;s cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named &quot;Timmy&quot; and &quot;Jimmy&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Books",
     "question": "The &quot;Berenstein Bears&quot; is the correct spelling of the educational children&#039;s book series&#039; name.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
